webcamclub.com 2015-03-19

# WebCamClub - Live Sex Web Cam Video Chat - Free Memberships, XXX Live Sex Girls

|   
---  

## for DynaSocial LLC Network of Websites

## 848 N Rainbow Blvd #3974

## +1.2094777676

## Effective Date: January 1st 2005

## Last Updated: January 14th 2013

  1. General
    1. The operative parties referred to in this policy are DynaSocial LLC (hereinafter referred to as "COMPANY"), and you, the user of this site.

      1. COMPANY, is the publisher and operator of the web sites [www.webcamclub.com](http://www.webcamclub.com/) and [www.webcamclub.tv](http://www.webcamclub.tv/) (hereinafter the "Webistes"). When first-person pronouns are used in this Policy, (us, we, our, ours, etc.) these provisions are referring to DynaSocial LLC d/b/a [www.webcamclub.com](http://www.webcamclub.com/) and [www.webcamclub.tv](http://www.webcamclub.tv/). Additionally, when the terms "the Websites" or "Websites" are used, these terms refer to [www.webcamclub.com](http://www.webcamclub.com/) and [www.webcamclub.tv](http://www.webcamclub.tv/).

      2. You, the User - As the user of these Websites, this policy will refer to the user as "you" or through any second-person pronouns, such as "yours," etc. Hereinafter, the user of the Websites shall be referred to in applicable second-person pronouns.

    2. This Privacy Policy describes how we use information received about you when you visit our Websites or when you subscribe to, or otherwise use our online services. This Policy does not cover any information that we may receive from or about you through channels other than through the use of the Websites.

  2. Revisions to this Policy

We reserve the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. You should periodically check for any modifications of this Policy by re-visiting this web page and using the "refresh" button on your browser. You should note the date of last revision to this Policy, which appears at the top of this Policy. If the "last modified" date remains unchanged after you have clicked the "refresh" button on your browser, you may presume that no changes have been made since the last reading of the policy. A changed "last modified" dates indicates that this Policy has been updated or edited, and the updated or edited version supersedes any prior versions immediately upon posting.

  3. Personal information that we collect

Visitors to our site and services will have multiple manners of interactivity with us. Depending upon your level of interaction, we will collect different information about you. The type of information collected is as follows: 

    1. Members - Members are those users who subscribe to our services will be prompted to provide their name, their address, their phone number, their e-mail address, their credit card number, and any other necessary billing information.

    2. Posters - Posters are visitors to our Website who choose to register to post information in our public forums. Minimal information is sought from Posters, and no actual personally identifying information must be submitted in order to become a Poster. Nevertheless, any information entered voluntarily by the Poster should be considered to be considered public information or information that is publicly available. If you do not wish for information to be made public, you should not enter it into your user profile when registering as a Poster.

    3. Browsers - Browsers are visitors to the site who never enter into any active data collection pages. Any information gathered from Browsers is also gathered from Posters and Members. This information is restricted to cookies, IP Addresses and Referral URLs, and other passive information gathering devises (explained below).

  4. How we collect information from you
    1. Passive Collection - We use cookies to collect information about you in order to enhance your experience on the site. The information collected in our cookies includes, but is not limited to, your user IP address, in order to determine the User’s geographic location as a means of fraud prevention.

    2. Active Collection - we collect information from you when you complete registration forms to sign up for your membership on our Website. Locations for such collection are registration pages, such as <http://www.webcamclub.com/register.php> but we reserve the right to add additional information collection portals.

  5. How we use your information

The primary use for your information is to provide you with services you have requested and/or paid for. We also use your information to deliver customized services to you. Non-personal and aggregate information, such as that collected passively is used in order to customize our marketing efforts or to customize the use of our site for an aggregate group of customers. We additionally will use the personal information of users whose membership has expired or have been cancelled in order to market our services to these individuals in the future.

We generally will use your information for the purposes for which you specifically provide it, for example, to ensure payment for subscription services. We also use your information for market research purposes - in order to increase your (and other users’) experience according to tracked interests, to analyze and target potential new markets, and for other marketing purposes.

  6. Special Cases.

It is our policy not to use or share the personal information about Visitors or Members in ways unrelated to those described in this Policy without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, we may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: 

    1. To satisfy any laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental, or legal requests for such information;

    2. To disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or other user policies;

    3. To operate our Services properly;

    4. To protect ourselves, our Members, and the general public. We specifically reserve the right to disclose any and all information to law enforcement in the event that a crime is committed, is suspected, or if we are compelled to do so by lawful criminal, civil, or administrative process, discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders, writs, or reasonable request of authorities or persons with the reasonable power to obtain such process.

    5. We will always cooperate with law enforcement authorities, private-party litigants, and others seeking information about our end users to the extent required by applicable law. Examples of such cooperation include lawful criminal, civil, or administrative process, discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders, writs, or reasonable request of authorities or persons with the reasonable power to obtain such process.

  7. Transmittals from Us

We may send You periodic email and/or SMS messaging communications that include, but are not limited to, announcements and exclusive offers related to Our existing and new programs. You may opt out of these announcements by contacting [support@webcamclub.com](mailto:support@webcamclub.com), or by clicking the opt-out link at the bottom of these communications. If You opt out of such communications, You may still receive account updates, support services and other information that is specifically related to the administrative operations of Your account via email. For example, We may send You communications confirming account activity, like password resets or tech support inquiries. Any such email notification will be issued to You from [support@webcamclub.com](mailto:support@webcamclub.com). If You provide Your information to Us, use the Site, or subscribe to any of Our services, You will have created a commercial relationship with Us. In having done so, You understand that even unsolicited commercial email sent from Us or Our affiliates is not SPAM as that term is defined under the law.

  8. Public Forums, Member Directories, and Internal Messaging:
    1. Public Forums - at the time of the instatement of this Policy, we offer public forums, which provide services that allow members to post messages to the public and the membership at large. In order to participate in a public forum, we may require information from our users such as a user name and password. Any information posted to a Forum should immediately be considered to be public information.

    2. Member Directories - Any information provided in a user profile, member directory, or other related service should be considered to be public information. We do not, cannot, and will not act to maintain the privacy of any information that you provide in any such forum or medium.

    3. Internal Messaging - We provide an internal messaging system for use between members of our Website. Any information that you send via this internal messaging system is not secure, and is not considered to be private information. You should use caution when sending any personal information over the internal messaging system, and you should not transmit any information that you would not wish to see disclosed to the general public.

  9. Our Commitment to Data Security.

We take measures, including data encryption, firewall, and the use of other in-house technologies to protect the transmission of all sensitive end-user information. We make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems. Nevertheless, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party ‘hackers’ from illegally obtaining this information. We take all reasonable measures to prevent such breaches of security, but given the resourcefulness of cyber-criminals we are unable to guarantee that our security is 100% breach-proof. You assume the risk of such breaches to the extent that they occur despite our reasonable security measures.

  10. How to Access or Modify Your Information.

We offer our Members the opportunity to access or modify information provided during registration. To access or modify such information, contact our Customer Service Department at [support@webcamclub.com](mailto:support@webcamclub.com).

  11. Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us at [support@webcamclub.com](mailto:support@webcamclub.com).

  12. E-Mail Removal

If you wish to opt-out of receiving all e-mail correspondence from us, you can enter your e-mail address below.
